{
    "timeLimit": 300,
    "numberOfQuestions": 4,
    "questions": [
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос1?",
            "a": "да",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "нет",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос2?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "да",
            "c": "нет",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос3?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "да",
            "correct": "c"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос4?",
            "a": "да",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "нет",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос5?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "да",
            "c": "нет",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос6?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "да",
            "correct": "c"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос7?",
            "a": "да",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "нет",
            "correct": "a"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос8?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "да",
            "c": "нет",
            "correct": "b"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос9?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "да",
            "correct": "c"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Вопрос10?",
            "a": "нет",
            "b": "нет",
            "c": "да",
            "correct": "c"
        }
    ]
}
